现在在Android Studio里你可以点击play这个按钮在你的设备上运行程序了
Now in Android studio you can hit the play button to run the app on your device.
在这个设备选择对话框里  你就可以看到已经连接的设备
In the device Chooser dialog. you should see your connected device.
如果默认使用设备进行调试  勾上这个复选框然后
To prevent the dialog from popping up in future times, check this box and
点击OK就好了  过不了多久你就能在你的手机上看到程序运行了
then hit OK to continue. Within a few moments you should see it on your phone.
另一方面  正如Raido之前提到过的  你可以使用命令行工具
On the other hand, as Raido was mentioning, you can use command line tools.
在项目的根目录下  使用gradlew命令来编译你的应用（适用于Mac和Linux平台）
From the root folder of the project, use grade lw to build your app on Mac or
如果你再用Windows系统  看一下视频下面的笔记
Linux. Check the link in the notes below if you're using Windows.
第一个命令是赋予gradlew这个命令执行权限
This first command grants execution permission to the gradlw rappers script. And
命令行编译的时候  这个工作你只需要做一次就好
you only need to do it the first time you're trying to build from the command
然后你可以调用./gradlew assembleDebug命令去debug  如果编译通过
line. Then you can call grade lw assemble debug. Once the build is successful,
在 app/build/apk 目录下就会生成一个APK文件
it creates an APK file at the app/build/apk directory. You can use
你可以用adb命令来安装  adb -r 这个参数意味着如果你之前安装了这个应用
adb to install the app. The -r command means that you can replace an existing
该命令可以强制替换重装  更多的adb命令行技巧
version of the app if you've already done it before. For more tips on adb,
你可以看一下下面的教师笔记  你可以使用adb命令里的
you can see the instructor notes below. Then you can use this adb command with
Activity管理工具启动主要的Activity  然后你就可以在
the activity manager tool in order to start the main activity. And there you see
设备上看到效果  它已经在我们的手机上运行了 哇哈哈
it on the device. And now we see it running in our phones. Woo hoo! Fist bump!
很顺利啊有木有  我们邀请Dan来帮我们设计程序的界面吧  哈哈
We're on a roll. Let's go find Dan so that we can build up the sunshine UI. Woo!